<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CSGO on Yesport</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/categories/csgo/</link><description>Recent content in CSGO on Yesport</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 14:49:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/categories/csgo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Makes Csgo an Esport Game</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/what-make-csgo-and-esport-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 14:49:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/what-make-csgo-and-esport-game/</guid><description>What are the things that makes CSGO one the greatest esport game? How this game keeps getting bigger while its getting older ? We will respond to all of thoses questions but first of all quick explanation of Counter Strike Rules.
Game banner taken from CSGO offical site
Rules Counter Strike is a shooting game in teams of 5 versus 5. To win the game you (and your team) need to win 16 rounds.</description></item><item><title>Ptits Cochons at Insalan 2023</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/insalan-ptits-cochons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 17:23:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/insalan-ptits-cochons/</guid><description>Yesport was invited to cover Ptits Cochons esport team in their trip to the &amp;lsquo;Insalan&amp;rsquo; of February 2023 !
Friday We got access to the event in advance thanks to Greg and his badge.
The atmosphere was soothing but weird, there was not a lot of players, the lan just opened and there was a lot a empty tables. But it was cool to be with players loving gaming in general and in the CSGO zone, players loving CSGO of course.</description></item><item><title>State of the French CSGO Scene in 2023</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/french-csgo-state-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:57:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/french-csgo-state-2023/</guid><description>Counter Strike is more alive than ever in France. With the Blast.tv Paris Major coming very soon, the French are hyped and ready.
Photo taken by HTLV.org, PGL Major Antwerp 2022
The Major Obviously, this year is the year of the Major. The CSGO Major, taking place in Paris and hosted by Blast.tv at the Accor Arena. It will be fantastic and incredible.
For the ones who don&amp;rsquo;t know what a major is : it&amp;rsquo;s the biggest and most anticipated tournament of the game.</description></item></channel></rss>