<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Yesport</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Yesport</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kackiest Kacky is back</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/kackiest-kacky-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/kackiest-kacky-is-back/</guid><description>banner credits
Kacky is a trackmania competitive which take place every year where the goal is to finish the more maps as possible during one month. The challenge seems easy but it is in fact very difficult. You may be wondering why “kacky”, what does this mean? Spoiler Alert, the trackmania player are very childish and pretty dumb. Kacky comes from German and when translate literally mean crazy, scatty but also and above all : shit, who sucks.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2023 is finally out !</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/spring-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/spring-2023/</guid><description>Banner by Ubisoft
Today, the Saturday first of April, the new Trackmania campaign is online. It’s quite an event, the old games were not updated or very rarely, so there was only one campaign and that forced the players to hunt the same maps again and again. So world records were very close and hard to get but they were pretty prestigious. But it all change with trackmania 2020 , because the game is recent, updates are possible.</description></item><item><title>What is Trackmania</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/what-is-track-mania/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/what-is-track-mania/</guid><description>Banner by Ubisoft
Trackmania is a racing game licence containing 4 games all developped by nadéo and edited by Ubisoft on PC, Playstation 4, Xbox one, Wii and DS. The first Trackmania game was released in 2003. The goal of the game is very simple: drive to the finish the fastest way possible, whatever the way.
The game developer are very lax, they don’t modify (or almost) the game and don’t correct the majority of bugs players find.</description></item><item><title>What Make Csgo and Esport Game</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/what-make-csgo-and-esport-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 14:49:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/what-make-csgo-and-esport-game/</guid><description>What are the things that makes CSGO one the greatest esport game? How this game keeps getting bigger while its getting older ? We will respond to all of thoses questions but first of all quick explanation of Counter Strike Rules.
Game banner taken from CSGO offical site
Rules Counter Strike is a shooting game in teams of 5 versus 5. To win the game you (and your team) need to win 16 rounds.</description></item><item><title>Ptits Cochons at Insalan 2023</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/insalan-ptits-cochons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 17:23:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/insalan-ptits-cochons/</guid><description>Yesport was invited to cover Ptits Cochons esport team in their trip to the &amp;lsquo;Insalan&amp;rsquo; of February 2023 !
Friday We got access to the event in advance thanks to Greg and his badge.
The atmosphere was soothing but weird, there was not a lot of players, the lan just opened and there was a lot a empty tables. But it was cool to be with players loving gaming in general and in the CSGO zone, players loving CSGO of course.</description></item><item><title>Women in E-sport</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/general/women_in_esport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 13:18:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/general/women_in_esport/</guid><description>I would like to be interested in this chronicle to women in esport.
We&amp;rsquo;ve talked a lot about major international competitions, but these mostly put men in the spotlight, like traditional sports competitions… For example, the broadcast of women’s football represents only 5% of the broadcast football in general.
As in many environments, this is a situation that is changing thanks to the perseverance of many women. They should have as much place as men in esports and play at a professional level.</description></item><item><title>What is Super Smash Bros. Ultimate ?</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/intro/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 11:37:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/intro/</guid><description>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate (SSBU), or just Smash for short, is a fighting game, released in 2018, developed by Sora Ltd, and Bandai Namco and published by Nintendo. It’s the fifth game of the Super Smash Bros Series. The games feature a lot of characters (up to 80 with DLC) from Nintendo Mascots, like Mario or Link, to third party franchises, like Minecraft or Final Fantasy.
Official nintendo banner for the game Nintendo.</description></item><item><title>Splatoon 3, and the difficulty of creating a healthy metagame</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/splatoon/splatoon-meta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:57:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/splatoon/splatoon-meta/</guid><description>Introduction During the 11th to 12 of January, the biggest online tournament of Splatoon 3, the 20XX, held its long-awaited fourth edition. The last one having reunited 128 teams from across the globe for a tremendous cash prize of $0USD.
Official logo of the 20XX
This community event highlights that despite a lack of real support from the game editor, Nintendo, the Splatoon competitive community continues to strive forward since the first iteration of the franchise, back in 2015.</description></item><item><title>State of the French CSGO Scene in 2023</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/french-csgo-state-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:57:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/csgo/french-csgo-state-2023/</guid><description>Counter Strike is more alive than ever in France. With the Blast.tv Paris Major coming very soon, the French are hyped and ready.
Photo taken by HTLV.org, PGL Major Antwerp 2022
The Major Obviously, this year is the year of the Major. The CSGO Major, taking place in Paris and hosted by Blast.tv at the Accor Arena. It will be fantastic and incredible.
For the ones who don&amp;rsquo;t know what a major is : it&amp;rsquo;s the biggest and most anticipated tournament of the game.</description></item><item><title>Why you shouldn't miss the TMGL</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/tmgl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 07:41:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/trackmania/tmgl/</guid><description>banner credit
For those who don’t know, the season 2023 of the Trackmania Grand League(TMGL for short) will start tommorow. Don’t miss it. For the sleepy head at the back of the classroom, i will resume what it is.
The tmgl is a trackmania tournament where 8 teams of 2 players compete. Those player comes from around the world but, this year, 31 % of players are french. The canadian player CarlJr will be present, if you don’t know him, he is arguably the best player of the world, he is the magnus karlsen or the Michael Jordan of Trackmania, he already won 6 world champion title.</description></item></channel></rss>