<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smash on Yesport</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/categories/smash/</link><description>Recent content in Smash on Yesport</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 09:33:23 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/categories/smash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The rules of the game in tournaments</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/rules-tournament/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 09:33:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/rules-tournament/</guid><description>To make sure everyone is on the same level of equity, there is rules that are established and are the sames in every tournament, and that&amp;rsquo;s what we will talk about today.
Victory conditions and items : For the items it’s simple : they are all banned. All of the items introduced random elements and that&amp;rsquo;s something that is horrendous for competitive play. The randomness of the items come even from how they appeared on the map : You have no way of knowing which items will spawn.</description></item><item><title>GUIDE: The attack in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate (Part 1).</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/attack-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 09:31:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/attack-guide/</guid><description>In Super Smash Bros Ultimate, There are a lot of different attacks for each character, and they all have the same pattern of inputs, to be used : a button and a direction on the left joystick. The button is used to determine the type of attacks, which we will talk about a bit later on. The joystick determines which attack of this type will be used and there are four possibilities.</description></item><item><title>What is Super Smash Bros. Ultimate ?</title><link>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/what-is-smash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 09:24:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://TheGregggg.github.io/yesport/posts/smash/what-is-smash/</guid><description>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate (SSBU), or just Smash for short, is a fighting game, released in 2018, developed by Sora Ltd, and Bandai Namco and published by Nintendo. It’s the fifth game of the Super Smash Bros Series. The games feature a lot of characters (up to 80 with DLC) from Nintendo Mascots, like Mario or Link, to third party franchises, like Minecraft or Final Fantasy.
The logo of Super Smash Bros Ultimate</description></item></channel></rss>